Parisa Dehbozorgi

UX/UI - Graphic & Motion Graphic Designer

Atlanta , GA 30305 / Phone: 470- 257- 9780 Email: parisadehbozorgi@gmail.com

<u>Linkedin</u>. <u>Portfolio</u>

Summary

UX/UI designer with extensive experience in Graphic and Motion Graphic Design.
Recently earned a professional certificate from Georgia Institute of Technology in Design Thinking, UX Research, UI Design & Guidelines and HTML, CSS and Javascript. Excellent at teamwork and highly motivated. Prioritization and Organization skills, thrive in a challenging environment.

Technical Proficiency

Programs: Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Aftereffect & XD.

Strong Knowledge/Strengths

Layout, Typography, Logo Design, Brochure and newsletter formatting, Motion Graphics, Website and Mobile app User flow, Wireframing, Prototyping, Information Architecture, Content structure, UI guidelines, CSS, HTML and Java.

UX/UI Projects

Travel App

Role: UX/UI Designer

Researching and Designing iOS mobile app. Scenario: Through field research on what pain points travelers have to make the itinerary and how they save the important information about their trips.

Website Redesign (U.S Environmental Protection Agency)

Role: UX/UI Designer

Scenario: According to the research and user testing we found the problems and the website pain points and simplified the website navigation and created the style guide based on brand directions.

Non Profit Website Redesign (COFAS.org) Role: UX/UI Designer

Redesigned and restructured the Cofas website.

Scenario: After research and analysis we made an information architecture and cart-sorting as a team. I guided the team as a ui designer to create and design user friendly and consistent webpages.

Previous Work Experience

Company: Button Art, Atlanta, GA

Position: Graphic Designer 08/2019 - Present Preparing & Redesigning more than 200 artworks for Gwinnett County. Developed the primary button sculpture. Initiated motion graphics, brochures, postcards & logo design.

Company: Respina Networks & Beyond, Iran

Position: Graphic Designer 10/2018 - 04/2019

To promote Internet and Phone services to companies
Designed Motion Graphics, Created Web & Print Design for
Digital Marketing, Proportioned Photos, Devised Infographics,
Web Banners, Formulated Online Design along with high
resolution Posters & Catalog designs

Company: SBG 02/2018 to 08/2018

Position: Graphic Designer, Location: Tehran, Iran SBG is a Provider in Surface engineering materials & solutions from Weld-Overlay, Thermal Spray and Clad Material.

Spearheaded print and web designs based on the headquarter guidelines. Designed and Layout posters, catalogs, stationeries and infographics. **Photo retouch for the website,** created web banners to help the company **showcase** the materials they sold and **highlighting** competitive advantages.

Company: Shiva Atlas Consultant, Architecture & Urban
Design 10/2013 to 04/2016

Position: Graphic Designer, Location: Tehran, Iran Design commercial and administrative complex, Hospital, Mega luxurious projects - worked cross functionally with Architecture, Structure and MEP Departments. Created all communications collateral, including web pages, brochures and fliers. Designed unique print materials, including Posters, brochures and logo design. Single handedly planned and produced marketing materials, including catalogs, handbooks and charts. Devised and launched annual reports.

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology

UX/UI Certificate

An intensive 24- week long boot camp. Skills learned consist of user research, user flow, visual wireframing, prototyping, user testing, user interface development.

Azad art and architecture - Tehran, Iran

Master of Graphic design

Sooreh - Shiraz, Iran

Bachelor of Graphic design